(Raj:)But, Daddy,
I-I miss my family so much,
(Raj:)and with you and Mummy
getting a divorce,
(Raj:)I feel sad and empty.
(Raj:)Buying a little toy
(Raj:)every now and then
helps me fill that void.
(Raj:)So while I can't
hug you every day,
(Raj:)flying that helicopter...
(Dr Koothrapalli:)I'm cutting you off.
(Raj:)Just to be clear,
financially or mid-sentence?
(Howard:)No red and yellow,
(Howard:)no red and yellow.
Yay!
It's green!
We did it!
Oh!
God, if it's this much fun to
rotate, imagine when we fly it.
(Howard:)Okay, now all I have to do
is rotate it vertically
(Howard:)until the lights turn off.
Oh, no!
Oh!
(Sheldon:)All right,
playtime's over.
(Howard:)Let's open
this baby up.
(Sheldon:)Won't that void the warranty?
(Howard:)Sheldon, I have a master's
degree in engineering.
(Howard:)I wipe my bottom
with warranties.